Jakah!
Let go of Heli.
If you want him, come and get him.
Jakah!
Chris, what are you doing?
I came to save you, Sooha.
From these vampires.
I'm the only one who believed you.
So you should trust me, too.
Have you forgotten whose
fault my death was?
You're not Chris.
Who are you?
Who do you think?
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
- That's Fate -
Damn...
I'm disappointed by how weak you are.
Do you want to meet the same fate again?
Who are you?
Why do you want Sooha?
Stay here.
Sooha, come here.
Is he a vampire?
Be careful.
Sooha!
Sooha, are you okay?
Heli, I...
That's not the Chris I know.
Chris isn't one of them...
He's not a vampire!
I'm sorry, Sooha.
This is what I am.
You can hate me if you want,
but can I flee with you for now?
I just want to take you someplace safe.
Heli!
Let go!
Why are you going with them?
Why don't you understand?
I'm doing this for you.
Solon!
Wolves?
Sooha!
Khan?
Solon!
They just keep coming.
Don't!
If you keep getting in my way,
I'll knock you out if I have to.
He's no ordinary vampire!
Let's hit him with everything we've got!
What?
Come on, while we have the chance.
You really don't know anything, do you?
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
Th-Thank you.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
We've kept our identities hidden
ever since we left the orphanage.
We just couldn't tell you.
You hating us scared us way more than
anyone else finding out we're vampires.
I'm sorry, Sooha.
Honestly, I'm confused.
I can't believe you're vampires.
You grew up at the orphanage
together, right?
How did you all become vampires?
Were you all bitten as children?
We don't know.
We've been vampires for as
long as we can remember.
It was an orphanage in name only.
We were actually imprisoned
and kept under close watch.
For a long time, that was our whole world.
We don't know anything for certain.
We don't know if we were
bitten or born this way.
Not only that, but unlike other vampires,
we're fine with sunlight and crosses.
Then how do you know you're vampires?
I know you have special powers,
but you could be different, like me.
We get the urge to drink blood.
We instinctively seek it out.
We don't want to eat anything else,
and we don't die if we don't.
But we only drink blood once a year.
On our birthday.
We only drink the blood of
recently deceased animals.
We've never hurt a person,
and we've never drunk human blood.
We swore to each other we wouldn't.
It's true. Please believe me.
No, you don't have to believe me.
I'll do my best to convince you.
Why did you come to save me?
I said those terrible things to you.
I felt like I had to.
Like I had to protect you.
Since the moment I first met you...
I've felt like that was my destiny.
Until then, I didn't know who
I was or how I should live.
But for the first time,
I felt like I'd found the answer.
I was born to protect you,
and I have to keep protecting you.
Heli...
Do you want to bite my neck?
What? We shouldn't do that!
I trust you.
Are you okay, Sooha?
Yeah. You barely put your mouth on me.
What about you?
You seem strained.
Did you want to drink my blood?
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't feel the impulse.
But not losing your
trust is more important.
I don't want to disappoint you.
You trusted me after learning what I am.
I don't want to betray you.
I'm not disappointed.
You've never betrayed me.
Until now, I've hated
vampires more than anything.
I thought they were dangerous
monsters who attacked people.
But you always came to my
rescue when I was in danger.
That made me really happy.
Knowing you're a vampire
won't make me hate you.
I'm sorry for saying those
awful things earlier.
You haven't changed
since the moment we met.
I'm glad we got to know each other more.
I hope you'll always be my friend.
Thank you.
Heli!
Jakah? Is that you, Jakah?
Yeah. That guy vanished.
Is Sooha all right?
Yeah. How about you guys?
Some minor injuries, but everyone's fine.
I see.
Should we come to you?
Oh... but Sooha wouldn't like that.
Heli, tell him we'll go to them.
Sooha!
Khan!
You're okay?
Yeah, thanks.
It's because you came to save me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, don't worry.
We're tough.
Oh, good.
Thanks for the help earlier.
Huh?
You don't need to thank us.
We couldn't ignore the situation, either.
Yeah.
Sooha, you probably saw earlier...
but we're actually werewolves.
Really?
Yeah.
You saw us back there, right?
Sorry for scaring you.
Everyone fears and avoids those
who are different from them.
We thought you'd hate us if you found out.
But we couldn't afford to
think about that back there.
We wanted to save you no matter what.
Khan, you guys...
Thank you for saving me.
When I saw Sooha get knocked down,
I felt a rage I'd never felt before.
Before I knew it, I'd turned into a wolf
and was charging toward him.
I've been meaning to tell you guys,
but I don't even know what I am.
You're Solon.
It was surprising, but it
doesn't change anything.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Well said, Jino.
Wait a minute.
Haven't we badmouthed werewolves a ton?
I did, too.
Aren't you really strong
when you turn into a wolf?
Oh, uh...
What else changes?
Your body temperature rises, right?
Who's faster, you or Jakah?
I've actually always wanted
to ride on a wolf's back!
Me, too!
Me, too.
And me!
Right?
Who wouldn't?
I'm definitely faster!
What are you, children?
Should we see who's faster?
Sooha! Heli!
Jakah.
Jaan.
Shion.
Noa.
Jino.
And Solon.
Thank you all so much.
Solon.
I'm sorry you had to reveal
your secret because of me.
I-It had nothing to do with you.
That guy just pissed me off.
I know, but I wanted
to say it nonetheless.
I'm sorry. And thank you.
There's something I want to tell you guys.
I don't hate you even if you're vampires.
I don't think you're different
from me even if you're werewolves.
I've hidden my unusual power until now,
but you accepted me the way I am.
That made me really happy.
So now, will you let me
do the same for you?
Of course.
Yeah.
We'd love to be friends.
Heck, let's become even better friends!
Yeah.
Enzy told me about you.
You should've told us sooner.
Man, Solon can be so weirdly stubborn!
Shut up.
I just can't figure it out.
Why did he look like my
childhood friend Chris?
You mean he's actually someone else?
Then who was that vampire?
We don't know yet,
but he's on another level from
the vampires we've faced until now.
Come to think of it, he said something
odd before he disappeared.
Something odd?
Yeah.
You really don't know anything, do you?
What does that mean?
He also said, "Do you want
to meet the same fate again?"
It almost sounded like
he'd fought us before.
Maybe he knows you guys.
To tell you the truth,
our friends keep going missing.
What?
Werewolves have always
been targeted by vampires.
It's gotten worse lately.
Our brothers are looking into it,
but they haven't found any
useful information yet.
And yesterday, we lost contact with them.
The girl from our school
who was attacked...
She was a werewolf, too.
The culprit hasn't been caught yet?
We assumed the victim was attacked by
a vampire because she was a werewolf.
But maybe we were wrong.
She looked just like Sooha.
So their actual target was Sooha?
The guy who attacked
today is the murderer?
It's possible.
Considering what happened today,
you should be careful, Sooha.
I don't know if that
vampire targeting Sooha
has anything to do with our
friends' disappearances,
but we'd all better be on guard.
Yeah.
Solon.
Thank you. You're the reason Sooha's safe.
No, I couldn't have done it alone.
But hearing you say that is, uh...
Sorry.
It must've been hard having
to keep that secret.
Telling everyone was
no big deal after all.
They all laughed it off.
Man, that's rude.
Right?
Sounds like them, though.
Yeah, I guess.
Next time, Episode 8:
"Old Moon: Vampire Lord."
- Vampire Lord -